<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<help>
    <login>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Signing In</h2>
        <div>
            The first time you use this app, you need to proceed with "Getting Started" where you choose your basic settings. Once these steps are finished, you can continue to sign in.<br/>
         If you are already registered on the web site of the same deployment, you can use the same username and password.<br/>
         If you check "Remember me" you won't have to enter these details next time again, until you sign out from the Dashboard.<br/>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        </div>
        ]]>
    </login>
    <get_started>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Selecting a Deployment</h2>
        <div>
        Before you use this app, you need to connect it to a deployment.<br/>
        You may either select a deployment from the list, or you type in the address. The pattern of the address is <em>www.example.com</em>, without "http://" or "https://" and without trailing slash. If you use a deployment from the list, keep the textfield empty.
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        </div>
        ]]>
    </get_started>
    <get_started_2>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Preferences</h2>
        <div>
        Select the language for the user interface and your preferred units (kilometres or miles).
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </get_started_2>
    <get_started_3>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Sign In or Sign Up</h2>
        <div>
        If you already have an account at the selected deployment, then you can continue to sign in. Otherwise, you will first have to create a new account.
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </get_started_3>
    <register>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Sign Up</h2>
        <div>
        Enter a username, a password and your email address. Before you can use your account on mycitizen.net, you will first need to confirm a link in an email that will come to your address.<br/>
        The password must be at least 8 characters long and contain a mix of numbers, upper case letters and lower case letters.
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </register>
    <forgot_password>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Forgotten Password</h2>
        <div>
        Enter the email address that you have used with your account at mycitizen.net. You will receive an email with a link, which you need to click to reset your password and create a new one.
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </forgot_password>
    <main>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Users, Groups and Resources</h2>
        <div>
        This is the main screen. If the filter is off, you see all users, groups and resources. If the filter is on, you see only those that match the filter settings.<br/>
        At the bottom you can open the <a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://filter">filter</a>, the <a href=netz.shodan.mycitizen://dashboard">dashboard</a> or your <a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://messages">messages</a>. The color of these button indicates their status.
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a hrefnetcz.shodan.mycitizen://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </main>
    <filter>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Filter</h2>
        <div>
        The filter affects the lists of users, groups and resources. There are several ways how to use it:<br/>
        <ul>
        <li>By checking "Only my connections", the list will only show your friends, the groups where you are a member, and resources that you are subscribed to.</li>
        <li>You can enter a part of the name, select tags, a language and a position on the map if you want to <a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://filter_map">filter by location</a>. The lists will then display only items that match all of the criteria. The function "filter by location" is only available if your phone is connected to the Internet.</li>
        <li>If you click on "Suggest", then the filter will be set according to your own profile. The lists will therefore show items that are similar to your own interests.</li>
        <li>The button "reset" clears all fields.</li>
        </ul>
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </filter>
    <filter_map>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Filter by Location</h2>
        <div>
        On this screen you can select a seach area on the map.
        <ul>
        <li>Show your own location, if available from GPS or networks.</li>
        <li>Show the center of the selected search area.</li>
        <li>Turn on to set a marker for the center of the search area. Turn off to return to moving and zooming the map.</li>
        <li>Remove the marker of the search area.</li>
        <li>Use the slider to change the radius of the search area.</li>
        </ul>
        When you have finished setting the search area, return to the {<FILTER>filter} screen and apply the filter.
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </filter_map>
    <dashboard>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Dashboard</h2>
        <div>
        On the Dashboard you find basic status information. The most important is the connection quality.<br/>
        You also can access the following functions:
        <ul>
        <li><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://profile">Edit your profile</a>.</li>
        <li><a href=netz.shodan.mycitizen://create_group">Create a group</a> - only available after being member for some time.</li>
        <li>Reload data from deployment</li>
        <li>Sign out (and forget username and password). If you just want to quite and keep your credentials, use the phone's "back" function.</li>
        </ul>
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a hrefnetcz.shodan.mycitizen://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </dashboard>
    <messages>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Messages</h2>
        <div>
        The message pane has two filters that show only new and only trashed messages. You can send new messages from the detail page of users.
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </messages>
    <user_detail>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>User Details</h2>
        <div>
             
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </user_detail>
    <group_detail>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Group Details</h2>
        <div>
             
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </group_detail>
    <resource_detail>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Resource Details</h2>
        <div>
             
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </resource_detail>
    <profile>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>My Profile</h2>
        <div>
        Here you can edit your personal information like name or description, your portrait, your tags (interests or topics that you are interested in) and your location. (This location will be visible to other users - they won't be able to see where you actually are right now.)
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </profile>
    <create_group>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>Creating a Group</h2>
        <div>
             
        </div>
    <br/><br/><a href="net.mycitizen.mcn://about">More information</a>
        ]]>
    </create_group>
    <about>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
    <h2>About</h2>
        Mycitizen.net is a free platform for local communities to support citizen engagement. The software for web and mobile is part of a non-profit project.
        <div>
        If you need more help, check out the <a href="https://mycitizen.net/manual:start">manuals </a> of <a href="https://mycitizen.net">mycitizen.net or
        <a href="{DEPLOYMENT_URL}/support">ask a question</a>. 
        <br/><br/><br/>
        (c) 2013ff. Burma Center Prague<br/>
        License: GPLv3<br/><br/>
        This project is supported from the resources of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of the Czech Republic within its Transition Promotion Program.
        </div>
        ]]>
    </about>
    <map>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Help</h1>
	<h2>Using the map</h2>
		Coming soon
        <div>

        </div>
        ]]>
    </map>
</help><!-- From: file:/Users/chris/AndroidstudioProjects/MyCitizen/app/src/main/res/xml/help_hlt.xml -->